netrider.net.au 2018-04-04

# Privacy Policy | Netrider

  *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   *   * 

__

### Welcome to Netrider ... Connecting Riders!

Interested in talking motorbikes with a terrific community of riders?  
Signup (it's quick and free) to join the discussions and access the full suite of tools and information that Netrider has to offer.

This privacy policy sets out how Netrider Pty Ltd, ABN 74 096 993 370, (herein known as Netrider) uses and protects any information that you provide, whilst using Netrider products and services. This includes, but is not limited to, netrider.net.au and any associated websites and sub-domains.

Netrider is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Any information provided by you to Netrider, by which you can be identified, will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy and applicable Australian law(s).

Netrider may change this policy as and when necessary. It is your responsibility to check this privacy policy periodically to ensure you agree with any changes.

### What information we collect

When using any products and services provided by Netrider, we may require some or all of the following information:

  * name
  * address
  * telephone number
  * email address
  * information related to any financial transactions which may be carried out
  * domain / Uniform Resource Locator (URL) where the software will be installed

Additionally, whilst using the Netrider website, any associated websites and sub-domains, some or all of the following information may be collected:

  * Internet Protocol (IP) address
  * geographical location
  * browser type and version
  * operating system
  * referral source
  * length of visit, page views, website navigation and any other related browsing activity

### What we do with the information we collect

The information you provide to Netrider is required for, but not limited to, the following reasons:

  * internal record keeping
  * access to the Netrider website, associated websites and sub-domains
  * account management
  * purchase confirmation and account reset
  * confirmation of email address
  * sending alerts, newsletters, and other relevant communications

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to Netrider is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect.

### Cookies and IP addresses

Netrider, any associated websites and sub-domains, use small text files, called cookies, to store information in your web browser. The information stored may include preferences, session identification, HTTP information, and IP address.

You can set your browser to not receive cookies, but this may limit your ability to use netrider.net.au and any associated websites and sub-domains.

IP addresses of computers used to visit Netrider, and any associated websites and sub-domains, are stored in our database. This includes when first registering for an account, managing your account details, writing a private or public message or performing any other transaction which results in data being transferred to or from your computer and the website in question.

### Links to other websites

Netrider, any associated websites and sub-domains, may contain links to other websites. These websites may or may not be affiliated with Netrider.

Netrider has no control over any external websites therefore clicking any link which results in you visiting an external website will result in this privacy policy no longer applying and Netrider cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites.

### Third Parties

Netrider, any associated websites and sub-domains, utilises and integrates third party software and services that collects limited information about users for security reasons. Information collected by these third parties is held in accordance with their privacy policies. For example, reCAPTCHA anti-spam information collected is held in accordance with the Google Privacy Policy.

### Controlling your personal information

When using Netrider services, you may choose to limit public viewing of applicable personal information through the settings located in the Privacy section of your account.

Netrider will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your explicit permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you security information, product updates, or other information pertaining to Netrider, or your account.

If you discover any of the information Netrider holds for you is incorrect or incomplete, that you are unable to change yourself, please contact us as soon as possible so the necessary changes can be made.

### Advertising

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to Netrider. Their cookies enable them and their partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to Netrider and/or other sites on the internet.

Netrider utilises third-party vendors and ad networks to serve advertising on our site. These vendors include [Google](https://www.google.com.au/ads/) and/or other Advertising Networks or Services. You may visit those vendors to opt out of the use of cookies for interest-based advertising. Alternatively, you may visit [aboutads.info](http://aboutads.info/) for further information about opting out.
